# DIANE KORONGY

I am a creative, technical solutions-driven full stack developer with a passion for design/UX, intuitive functionality, and accessibility for all. With experience in Rails, Javascript, React/Redux, iOS, my goal is to build meaningful products and contribute in teams.

## **EDUCATION**

Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ

BS in Information Technology with a minor in Statistics & Computer Science

May 2017

Flatiron School, New York, NY

March 2019

Full Stack Web Development/Software Engineering Immersive Program

#### RELEVANT SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Javascript (ES6), Ruby, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, Swift/iOS, R, SAS
- Libraries & Frameworks: React, Redux, jQuery, ExpressJS, Rails
- Tools & Platforms: Git, PostgresSQL, MySQL, Heroku, Firebase, Adobe Suite, Invision, Sketch
- Other: Technical Support, Project Management, Enterprise Client Relations/Support, Handling escalations, integrations

### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

- + CANDID github | demo link Social E-learning platform/interview prep for developers and techs. React/Redux, user authentication/OAuth, Firebase database integration with custom routing
- Let's Spoon github I demo link A Tinder-like swiping web app that matches users based on food preferences. Utilizing React, Yelp API, React-Spring-Hooks, Leaflet Maps API, Rails, Postgres
- + Astrodom gitub I demo link Single page educational game application intended for (children) to learn the Javascript event loop/call-stack. Made with Vanilla Js/Rails API/Postgres

### **EXPERIENCE**

iCIMS. Holmdel. NJ

Technical Support Engineer

## June 2017 - July 2018

- Assisted in the configuration, adoption, maintenance, and support of iCIMS ATS software at client's request
- Managed multiple concurrently running projects and client accounts while delivering a customer experience second to none
- Worked to troubleshoot, recreate, QA test, detect and escalate software bugs Proficient in JIRA, Salesforce, HRIS, CRM
- Assisted in defining client business processes, best practices, co-manage implementation projects, train users, and facilitate overall success within various client organizations.
- Supported clients and users through troubleshooting, ticket creation and execution, asset management and training
- Partnered with external vendors to configure and troubleshoot client integrations via Flat File and web services, API integrations
- Mentored and created new trainings/ designed training to support new hire classes and internal teams

## Geek Squad, Manalapan, NJ

Consultation Agent

## Jan 2016 - Feb 2017

- Educated clients hands on the proper use of old and new/advanced technologies through training appointments
- Led in individual NPS and service sales by ensuring the best services and technology solutions to customers
- Ran troubleshooting tests and diagnostics to determine product needs and service solutions on client's malfunctioning tech
- Replacement of nonfunctional hardware components and diagnostic for proper functionality, OS reinstallation and proper setup, software installation, virus removal, troubleshooting computers network connection and proper setup for optimal connectivity
- Data retrieval from non-functional Internal or External HDD's, flash drives
- Handled technical troubleshooting within an enterprise environment, including system crashes, slow-downs and data recoveries

### Dow Jones, Princeton, NJ

QA Analyst, Knowledge & Training, and Customer Experience (Intern)

## June 2016 - Aug 2016

- Record and report software bugs and usability problems to project managers for corrective action
- Worked on the design, develop, and evaluation of training programs
- Performed of a wide variety of planned clinical oriented functions and learning experiences
- ACHIEVEMENTS, Dow Jones Business Plan Competition Winner Designed a high-fidelity user experience and interface of a mobile app prototype for The Wall Street Journal